<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:ns1="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <color name="accent">#714FFF</color>
    <color name="accent_2">#FF2E93</color>
    <color name="black">#FF000000</color>
    <color name="color_item_menu_normal">#000000</color>
    <color name="color_item_menu_selected">#714FFF</color>
    <color name="color_upgrade_background">#044251</color>
    <color name="error">#E6514E</color>
    <color name="primary">#000000</color>
    <color name="primary_dark">#000000</color>
    <color name="white">#FFFFFFFF</color>
    <color name="white_50">#80FFFFFF</color>
    <string name="a_reset_password_email">A reset password email will be sent to the email address below</string>
    <string name="account">Account</string>
    <string name="app_name">Kaizen VPN</string>
    <string name="by_signing_up_i_agree_to">By signing up, I agree to the Privacy Policy and Term of Conditions</string>
    <string name="com.google.firebase.crashlytics.mapping_file_id" ns1:ignore="UnusedResources,TypographyDashes" translatable="false">00000000000000000000000000000000</string>
    <string name="comfirm_password">Comfirm password</string>
    <string name="connect_vpn_now">connect vpn now</string>
    <string name="connecting">Connecting (%s)</string>
    <string name="description_slide_1">Thank you for downloading Kaizen Vpn App. We hope you Like it , Enjoy it, Share it.</string>
    <string name="description_slide_2">Select your favorite themes to find your the Kaizen Vpn</string>
    <string name="description_slide_3">Sign in and be one of our community and share your Kaizen Vpn with others</string>
    <string name="description_slide_4">Download and keep it on your phone, share and use it when you want :) And Don\'t Forget to Share it with Friends and Family :)</string>
    <string name="description_slide_5">Add your favorites Ringtones to your favorite list and use it later when you want :) And Don\'t Forget to Share it with Friends and Family :)</string>
    <string name="description_slide_6">Browse best Ringtones of Samsung collection and give your rating</string>
    <string name="description_slide_7">Download and share any Samsung Ringtone from the app to any social network</string>
    <string name="description_slide_8">Go PRO and enjoy with apps without any ads ,with a small price .</string>
    <string name="developer_email">vpn@kaizenvpn.com</string>
    <string name="disconnect_vpn">disconnect vpn</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="email_address">Email address</string>
    <string name="enjoying_our_app_your_feedback">Enjoying our app? Your feedback matters! Please take a moment to leave a rating and share your thoughts. Thank you for your support!</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="free">Free</string>
    <string name="gcm_defaultSenderId" translatable="false">682842137386</string>
    <string name="google_api_key" translatable="false">AIzaSyBpK4ColXCwXt6gzvRhudufO8sDR1roy9Q</string>
    <string name="google_app_id" translatable="false">1:682842137386:android:834ecc53802315165f7453</string>
    <string name="google_crash_reporting_api_key" translatable="false">AIzaSyBpK4ColXCwXt6gzvRhudufO8sDR1roy9Q</string>
    <string name="google_storage_bucket" translatable="false">kaizenvpn-com.appspot.com</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="invalid_email_please_try_again_or_use_the_new_one">Invalid email. Please try again or use the new one</string>
    <string name="leave_your_rating">Leave Your Rating</string>
    <string name="log_out">Log out</string>
    <string name="monthly">Monthly</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="only_show_vip_servers">Only Show VIP Servers</string>
    <string name="password_doesn_t_match">Password doesn’t match</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_des">Kaizen VPN LLC. (the “Company”) is committed to maintaining robust privacy protections for its users. Our Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) is designed to help you understand how we collect, use and safeguard the information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our Service.
        \n\nFor purposes of this Agreement, “Service” refers to the Company’s service which can be accessed via our website at https://Kaizen_VPNapp.com/ or through our mobile applications on the App Store and Play Store in which users can capture quick reaction videos instantly. The terms “we,” “us,” and “our” refer to the Company. “You” refers to you, as a user of Service. By accepting our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use (found here: https://Kaizen VPNapp.com/terms, you consent to our collection, storage, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.
        \n\nI – PROCESSING YOUR DATA
        \n\nKaizen VPN processes user data to a limited scope – for provision of the Services. We process the following basic information:
        \n\n1.1 INFORMATION FOR CREATING YOUR ACCOUNT:
        \n\nEmail address. We ask for your email address as part of your registration. It is necessary for establishing a Kaizen VPN account and using our Services. 1.2 INFORMATION COLLECTED We collect only your email, which you submit to us through the registration process at the app. II – HOW WE USE AND SHARE INFORMATION We do not share your personal information with third parties. III- HOW WE PROTECT INFORMATION We implement security measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access.Your account is protected by OTP code sending to your email and we urge you to take steps to keep your personal information safe by not disclosing your password and by logging out of your account after each use. We further protect your information from potential security breaches by implementing certain technological security measures including encryption, firewalls, and secure socket layer technology. However, these measures do not guarantee that your information will not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software. By using our Service, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to assume these risks. IV- YOUR RIGHTS REGARDING THE USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION You have the right at any time to prevent us from contacting you for marketing purposes. When we send a promotional communication to a user, the user can opt-out of further promotional communications by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in each promotional email. You can also indicate that you do not wish to receive marketing communications from us in the “Settings” section of the Site. Please note that notwithstanding the promotional preferences you indicate by either unsubscribing or opting out in the Settings section of the Site, we may continue to send you administrative emails including, for example, periodic updates to our Privacy Policy. V- LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES As part of the Service, we may provide links to or compatibility with other websites or applications. However, we are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by those websites or the information or content they contain. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by us through the Site and the Service. Therefore, this Privacy Policy does not apply to your use of a third-party website accessed by selecting a link on our Site or via our Service. To the extent that you access or use the Service through or on another website or application, then the privacy policy of that other website or application will apply to your access or use of that site or application. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of other websites before proceeding to use them. VI- CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY The Company reserves the right to change this policy and our Terms of Service at any time. We will notify you of significant changes to our Privacy Policy by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. Significant changes will go into effect 30 days following such notification. Non-material changes or clarifications will take effect immediately. You should periodically check the Site and this privacy page for updates. VII- CONTACT US If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the practices of this Site, please contact us by sending an email to hello@Kaizen VPNapp.com Last Updated: This Privacy Policy was last updated on Dec 20, 2023.</string>
    <string name="project_id" translatable="false">kaizenvpn-com</string>
    <string name="rate">Rate</string>
    <string name="recurring_billing_cancel_anytime"><![CDATA[Recurring Billing. Cancel anytime. Payment will be charged to your iTunes account at confirmation of purchase. Your subscription automatically renews unless auto-renew is turned off at least 24 hours before the end of the current period. Your account will be charged for renewal within the 24 hours prior to the end of the current period. You can manage your subscription and switch off auto-renewal by accessing your iTunes & App Store Account Settings after purchase.]]></string>
    <string name="refuse">Refuse</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="reset_password">Reset password</string>
    <string name="reset_password_email">Reset password email</string>
    <string name="save_2_month_free">save 2 month free</string>
    <string name="select_a_location">Select a Location</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use">terms of use</string>
    <string name="there_is_no_ads_anymore_awesome">There is no Ads anymore Awesome connection speed Multiple device usage Watch high quality video</string>
    <string name="title_slide_1">Welcome To \nKaizen Vpn</string>
    <string name="title_slide_2">We are using Tags</string>
    <string name="title_slide_3">Be an Author</string>
    <string name="title_slide_4">Download Kaizen Vpn</string>
    <string name="title_slide_5">Add to Favorite</string>
    <string name="title_slide_6">Rate Kaizen Vpn</string>
    <string name="title_slide_7">EASY TO SHARE</string>
    <string name="title_slide_8">Remove ads</string>
    <string name="upgrade_to_vip">PREMIUM</string>
    <string name="upgrade_vip">Upgrade VIP</string>
    <string name="upload">Upload</string>
    <string name="we_sent_a_reset_password_email_to_your_inbox">We sent a reset password email to your inbox. Please check and click the link inside to set up your new password</string>
    <string name="yearly">Yearly</string>
    <string name="you_current_xxx">You current %s VIP package is valid until %s. If you want to cancel or change, please go to your subscription account</string>
    <style name="AppBodyText">
        <item name="android:textSize" ns1:ignore="SpUsage">14dp</item>
        <item name="android:fontFamily">@font/worksans_bold</item>
        <item name="android:textColor">@color/white</item>
    </style>
    <style name="AppButton">
        <item name="android:layout_width">match_parent</item>
        <item name="android:layout_height">48dp</item>
        <item name="android:background">@drawable/background_button_selector</item>
        <item name="android:gravity">center</item>
        <item name="android:textAllCaps">true</item>
        <item name="android:letterSpacing">0.14</item>
        <item name="android:textSize" ns1:ignore="SpUsage">13dp</item>
        <item name="android:textAppearance">@style/AppBodyText</item>
    </style>
    <style name="AppCheckBox" parent="Theme.AppCompat">
        <item name="colorAccent">@color/white</item>
        <item name="android:textColorSecondary">@color/white</item>
    </style>
    <style name="AppContentText">
        <item name="android:textSize" ns1:ignore="SpUsage">14dp</item>
        <item name="android:fontFamily">@font/worksans_regular</item>
        <item name="android:textColor">@color/white</item>
    </style>
    <style name="AppProgressBar" parent="Theme.AppCompat">
        <item name="colorAccent">@color/accent_2</item>
    </style>
    <style name="AppTitleText">
        <item name="android:textSize" ns1:ignore="SpUsage">16dp</item>
        <item name="android:fontFamily">@font/worksans_bold</item>
        <item name="android:textColor">@color/white</item>
    </style>
    <style name="Base.Theme.WitVPN" parent="Theme.Material3.Light.NoActionBar">
        
        <item name="colorPrimary">@color/primary</item>
        <item name="colorPrimaryDark">@color/primary_dark</item>
        <item name="android:windowBackground">@color/primary_dark</item>

        <item name="android:windowIsTranslucent">true</item>
    </style>
    <style name="DialogAnimation">
        <item name="android:windowEnterAnimation">@android:anim/fade_in</item>
        <item name="android:windowExitAnimation">@android:anim/fade_out</item>
    </style>
    <style name="ProgressDialogStyle">
        <item name="android:windowBackground">@drawable/background_progress_dialog</item>
        <item name="android:navigationBarColor">@color/black</item>
        <item name="android:statusBarColor">@android:color/transparent</item>
        <item name="android:windowTranslucentStatus">true</item>
    </style>
    <style name="Theme.WitVPN" parent="Base.Theme.WitVPN"/>
    <declare-styleable name="InputView">
        <attr format="string" name="iv_label"/>
        <attr format="string" name="iv_hint"/>
        <attr name="android:inputType"/>
        <attr format="enum" name="iv_action">
            <enum name="NONE" value="0"/>
            <enum name="CANCEL" value="1"/>
            <enum name="HINT" value="2"/>
        </attr>
        <attr format="boolean" name="state_error"/>
    </declare-styleable>
</resources>